A violent past. A man on the edge.
As Good as Dead is a action, crime film directed by R. Ellis Frazier.
An ex-cop in self-imposed witness protection in Mexico becomes a
target when a fight video of his apprentice goes viral.
Sonny Kilbane, played by Tom Berenger.
Bryant, played by Michael Jai White.
Piro, played by Louis Mandylor.
Heather, played by Gillian White.
Eric, played by Michael Copon.
Marisol, played by Gabriella Quezada.
As Good as Dead is a 2022 Mexican crime action film
written by Michael Jai White, directed by R.
Ellis Frazier and starring White and Tom Berenger.
The film explores themes of affectation, curious,
aggressive, domineering, admiring.